Hello Gas welcome to the video stock
market friends, the March
quarter financial results have been presented by Mudra,
both the standard and consolidated results have been out, we will
discuss this video today, friends let's
start the video, so Gas, here the
final dividend from the company has also been
recommended here at 1.25 per
equity share, which will be done in the Annual General Meeting
and here we go now to the
financial results of the company, guys,
here we have come, the
consolidated financial results and the
numbers given in millions, the income is 78.9 crores, the
previous quantum was 62.3 crores and on March
22 order it was 45.4 crores, the
income quarter on quarter, air on air, there is a
rise in both, the
expenditure is 58.5 crores, in the previous quarter it was
44 crores, in the March 22 quarter there was an
expenditure of 31 crores, here the expenditure of the
company has also increased,
along with the income, here the expenditure is also  There has been an
increase in the quadran quarter. If we
talk about operating profit in Air, then there is an
operating profit of 20 crores. In the previous
quadrant 22, there was an operating profit of 13.7 crores. There has been an
increase in the operating profit. If
we talk about net profit, then it is 15.8 crores.
In the previous quarter, there was 15 crores. In the March 22 quarter, there was a profit of 1 crore. There was a quadran
growth in the profit quarter. Excellent growth is also being seen in Air on Air. In the
last quarter of 2.06, very strong growth has been seen here since last year. So,
if you look at the result of the company
here, then very excellent results have been seen here.
Talking about the segment, the company is
generating new external sales here, which
can be seen here. The
income of the company has been seen to be very excellent here.
Now, the external sales here, which
means trust, services,
enterprise solutions, is
generating revenue from both of these and we will go ahead with the
company.  On the standard on
results, the numbers are given in millions, the income was
48 crores, the previous quarter was 45 crores, the
MAS 22 quadrant had an income of 41 crores, the
income is quarter on quarter, there is a rise in both, there was an
expenditure of 42
crores, 39 crores,
27 crores in the
last quarter, the expenses will also be seen here, due to a
lot of back the company did
not grow that well in profits, but there has been a huge decline in
expenses in the on-year also, due to this the
profit this time was 4 crores, in the last quarter it
was 4.5 crores, in the MAS 202 quarter there was a
profit of 11.2 crores, there will be a decline quarter on
quarter, there has been a
decline in profit in around air also, there is a
decline of 0.53 from apps from the previous quarter, there is a
decline from last year also, so
if you see the result of the company here,
in consolidated dated, you will see good average results here
because the
profit is continuously declining, so now let
us do the video here and
if  If you have any doubts, ask in the comment section. See you next time.